http://www.dr-sauer.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Website Privacy Policy
Key details
This website privacy policy describes how it protects and makes use of the information you give the company when you use this website. If you are asked to provide information when using this website, it will only be used in the ways described in this privacy policy.
This policy is updated from time to time. The latest version is published on this page. This website privacy policy was updated on: 30.08.2017
If you have any questions about this policy, please email london@dr-sauer.com or write to: Dr. Sauer & Partners, 11 Langley Avenue, Surbiton, Surrey, KT6 6QH
Introduction
We gather and use certain information about individuals in order to provide products and services and to enable certain functions on this website. We also collect information to better understand how visitors use this website and to present timely, relevant information to them.
What data we gather
We may collect the following information:
Name and job title
Contact information including email address
Demographic information, such as postcode, preferences and interests
Website usage data
Other information relevant to client enquiries
Other information pertaining to special offers and surveys
How we use this data
Collecting this data helps us understand what you are looking for from the company, enabling us to deliver improved products and services.  Specifically, we may use data:
For our own internal records.
To improve the products and services we provide.
To contact you in response to a specific enquiry.
To customise the website for you.
To send you promotional emails about products, services, offers and other things we think might be relevant to you.
To send you promotional mailings or to call you about products, services, offers and other things we think might be relevant to you.
To contact you via email, telephone or mail for market research reasons.
Controlling information about you
When you fill in a form or provide your details on our website, you may see one or more tick boxes allowing you to:
Opt-in to receive marketing communications from us by email, telephone, text message or post.
If you have agreed that we can use your information for marketing purposes, you can change your mind easily, via one of these methods:
Sign in to our website and change your opt-in settings.
Send an email to london@dr-sauer.com
Write to us at: Dr. Sauer & Partners, 11 Langley Avenue, Surbiton, Surrey, KT6 6QH
We will never lease, distribute or sell your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or the law requires us to. Any personal information we hold about you is stored and processed under our data protection policy, in line with the Data Protection Act 1998.
Security
We will always hold your information securely. To prevent unauthorised disclosure or access to your information, we have implemented strong physical and electronic security safeguards. We also follow stringent procedures to ensure we work with all personal data in line with the Data Protection Act 1998.
Links from our site
Our website may contain links to other websites.  Please note that we have no control of websites outside the www.dr-sauer.com  domain. If you provide information to a website to which we link, we are not responsible for its protection and privacy.
Always be wary when submitting data to websites. Read the site’s data protection and privacy policies fully.
